Hey, hey, what's up, my friend? So, if
you have been trading for a while now,
you know, trying different strategies,
systems, indicators, patterns, but still
you've not yet achieved consistent
profitability, then today's video is for
you. Many years ago, right, when I
started trading, my first trading system
was using Bollinger Bands. You know,
I'll wait for the price to come towards
the lower Bollinger Band, then when the
price bounced higher, I would then sell,
usually around the upper Bollinger Band.
And with this approach, this system that
I first tried, I had three winning
trades in a row. At this point, I had
thoughts like, man, this is it. This is
life or wife-changing money. I can't
tell anyone about this system, or at
least, you know, they erode my edge,
they erode my profitability. So, those
were the thoughts that I have. And it
seems like I was guarding this secret as
though it's my recipe to my
grandmother's chicken rice. And guess
what? The next five trades were losers.
So, I do what 90% of traders do. I
concluded that this strategy, this
system isn't working, and I went on to
look for something better. So, this is
kind of like, you know, blaming the gym
equipment, right? When you can't see
your abs after a single workout. Yeah.
So, shortly after I chanced upon
harmonic patterns. You know, it's a
trading method where you use tools like
Fibonacci retracement and extensions to
draw complex patterns called, you know,
things like crab, bat, butterfly, etc. I
spent about a good 6 months learning how
to draw these patterns. You know, that's
because I'm kind of a slow learner, if
you ask me. And guess what? The same
damn thing happened. You know, I
experienced a few winning trades at the
start, and then shortly afterwards, the
losses come in and hit me harder right
than my wife's reaction, you know, when
I told her I got another trading course.
So, again, the voice in my head says
things like, you know, this trading
strategy doesn't work. Let's look for
something else.
So, I went around, you know, searching
for the holy grail. You know, I've tried
things like different indicators, chart
patterns, candlestick patterns. You
know, I know more Japanese candlestick
names right than actual
Japanese words. And the results were
more or less the same. It's always
a few wins followed by the losses, blame
the strategy, rinse, and repeat itself.
At this point, I'm starting to doubt
myself. I have questions like, "Why does
this always happen? Why am I not getting
consistent results like the guy on
YouTube called Rayner?" Or why do I make
money at the start only to lose it all
eventually? And do you know
what I realized? [music] I realized that
the problem
lies
with me.
That's right. I am the problem. That's
because I was hopping from one trading
system to another like monkey, you know,
swinging through trees.
My actions were inconsistent, and this
explains my inconsistent results.
Because if your actions are
inconsistent, guess what? Your results
results will be
inconsistent. So, the bottom line is
this. It's that if you want to be a
consistent trader, then you must have a
consistent set of actions. Find a proven
trading system that works and stick to
the rules.
No exceptions. No situations like, you
know, "But the market looks different
today." No, "I have a good feeling about
this one." If you can do this, right,
then consistent profitability isn't far
away. And if you want to learn proven
trading systems that work, then you can
actually grab my free training over
here. Just go down to
tradingwithrayner.com/go.
Okay? And you can get this
free 54-minute training where I will
share with you three proven trading
systems that work backed by 25 years of
data. You'll learn things like a mean
reversion trading system that has
generated 2,834%
over the last 25 years. You'll learn the
trend following system. You'll learn a
momentum trading system. And I'll send
you this uh
PDF slides of the training, the cheat
sheet, the back test reports all to your
inbox for free. So, if you want to grab
a copy of this training, just go down to
tradingwithrayner.com/go.
I'll put the link somewhere below below
this video so you can grab a copy of it.
So, with that's it. I wish you good
luck, good trading.
Talk to you soon.